question_data = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, it is possible to capture Elder Dragons.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}

